Friends, this is the
Amazon Pay credit card from ICICI Bank.  This
credit card has so many benefits, so many
advantages and because there are no fees,
I think this is the kind of best credit card.
I will also tell you what are some of the benefits
and will count the things one by one.
You yourself will say that
you must have this.  The first and the
best thing is that there is
no joining fee for this.  You
can also apply directly from Amazon's application.
I have made the complete procedure for you on how to apply in the previous video.
You go and check it.  Yes, you will get the limit
according to your civil score and your
past transactions.
But then the benefits start
that there is no joining fee and no annual fee.
There is no fee for this, you
can just hold it.  NFC is also available
in it, so you can also tap and pay with it.  You can
use it directly from the application and
can also control it.
You can also register it on ICICI Bank application.
Also,
if you look at all the basic level cards, there is a joining fee of ₹500
which is waived off
later by giving some offers
or there is also an annual fee in which
you have to spend a certain amount
in a year, after which it is waived off and you
get that too through reward points,
if you convert it into cash then
some charges are levied and if you
want to buy something with it then a forced purchase is made.  There are
no such scenes here.
Brother, there is no joining fee and there will be no annual fee either.
And
if I compare the rest of the cards, I have
more cards.  Axis Bank has a Flipkart
card.  Apart from that, I
also have cards of HDFC and SBI.  One thing
I have seen common in all of them is that the reward
points have an expiry
date.  There is nothing like that in it.
Got reward points.  Got the rewards.
You can use it whenever you want.   The
next thing is that whatever cash benefits you get through
discounts are directly
transferred to your Amazon Pay.  There is
no such thing as converting reward points.  There are
separate points, you can use them separately.  And
this reward earning, you have the
complete application of Amazon.  There are more than 10 crore
products there, you can use them to buy.  There is
a certain balance on Amazon Pay
that if you have
deposited something from the bank then you can withdraw it also.
But if you have received some cashback then
you cannot withdraw it.  But you
can use it.  Recharge it
or you know that on Amazon you
can recharge it or you
can go and buy some stuff.  You can do everything
there.  Now, as I have
also taken membership of Amazon Prime,
whatever I buy from Amazon.in,
whatever I buy from Indian Amazon, I get an additional cashback of 5%.
So for Flipkart,
whoever accesses it, brother gives you 10%
cashback.  Here's where Amazon does it.
Gives only 5%.  But you will get cashback only if you are a Prime member,
if you are not a Prime member then
you will get only 3% cashback.  Think about this a little.
However, if you hold this card,
you will keep getting such offers for a long time
that you will get the 3-month membership of ₹699
or the 1-month membership
of Amazon Prime for free.
So the advantage of having this card is
that sometimes you get offers etc.
And ultimately Prime membership will become
free.  If you purchase too much of it.
Meaning people
purchased it for their friends also.  I did it for myself also
and if you add 3-3%, you will get so much
cashback that you can take Prime membership
and after that you can avail more cashback.
Now there are many Amazon Pay merchant
partners, which means there
are more than 100, if you use this card on them then
you will get 2% cashback there
also and 1% if you use it anywhere, that is even if you go
internationally and use it then
also you will get 1% discount
cashback.  Yes, do
not use it for fuel.  Now why is this so?
However, if you are not using a credit card for a particular fuel like
Power Place etc.  If
you are using a General Axis Bank
or any other bank
credit card which is
not for fuel, then it is similar to them
because here you will be charged 2%
surcharge and then that 1% will be waived off, so
you are paying 1% extra.  But if you are
using a credit card
which is related to fuel, then you have
more benefits there, so do not use it for fuel.
Now along with the benefits,
know about some charges also.  Its annual fee and
joining fee are nil.  But if you
ever withdraw cash, that is, if you
withdraw money from an ATM, you will be
charged 3.75% per month.  So
remember, you are giving returns of around 40%
annually, hence avoid withdrawing cash.  There are
also cash-based credit cards that are given to you for a certain period of time.
You pay for that.  You do
not incur extra charges.  But be
careful in this.  Along with this, those people who
pay the minimum due say that the
bill is very big.  I can't pay right now.  I will
pay the minimum dues.
Remember, you have paid the minimum pay due and from the next
day onwards, the remaining amount will also be
charged at 3.75% per month, meaning it becomes
like cash.  Those charges start getting levied.
So again you are giving a return of 40%
x interest rate.  So this thing has to be kept in
mind.  Do not cash.  Minimum
due is not to be paid.  You have to pay the full amount.
And if you pay the bill late, that is, if you
delay a little from the due date, then there is a
bracket of ₹100 to ₹1300 in which
you may be charged different types of charges.
So keep this in mind as well.
So brother, these were some of its benefits and
I also tried to tell you
how the fees are charged.  If you have any
question then write it in the comment section.
Rest, please do let me know how much you like this card.